# FIRDOS ANSARI

# System Engineer - WMOS

## **PROFILE**

Dedicated professional with extensive experience in maintaining and enhancing the application side of Manhattan WMOS SCPP & Classic Version. Skilled in analysis, design, and testing of Manhattan WMOS, with a focus on post-implementation solution consulting

# CONTACT

- +91 9960017523
- ansarifirdos222@gmail.com
- in Firdos ansari
- GitHub

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Pune University**

2020 - 2022

MCA - Masters of Computer App.

#### **ACS College Narayangaon Pune**

2017 - 2022

B.Sc. - Bachelor of Science

## SKILLS

- Manhattan WMS-2016
- MySQL
- Unix / Linux
- Java
- Jasper Report Development
- Supply Chain Management
- Scripting / Shell Scripting
- JavaScript
- Spring Boot

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Hudson's Bay Company - WMOS**

August 2022 - Present

- Maintaining the application side of the Manhattan WMOS SCPP
  & Classic Version.
- Experienced in Analysis, design and Testing of Manhattan WMOS.
- Post implementation solution consulting for Manhattan WMOS.
- Analysis root cause & resolving critical issues in various areas of WMS.
- Worked on Procedures and Scripts depending on the business requirements and automate few business scenarios.
- Worked on critical production issues related Cycle count, MHE Inbound/Outbound, Waving & various areas of WM.
- Worked on P1, P2 issues for DC like, Printer issue, RF gun scanning issue, Picking and packing issue, Manhattan application
- Worked on ESP & UC4 Job scheduler. Mainframe monitoring Scripts analysis finding root cause of ESP Job failures
- Actively worked on weekend shift on call and support extended hours during issue times.
- I have good understanding of Jasper reports development and Configuration as per business requirement.
- Worked on Import Accounting system of the company for calculation of custom duty payment to the Canadian government. I was only SME for resolution of tickets and the system issues.

# Acciojob - Full Stack Web Developer Trainee

January 2022 - August 2022

- Learning data Structures and algorithm with java as a language. With focus on solving leetcode problems with optimal solution.
- Learned spring boot with real life projects implementing core java functionality like OOP's Concept.